Are you Jake Sully?
I'd like to talk to you about a fresh start, on a new world.
You'd be making a difference.
I became a marine for the hardship.
I told myself I could pass
any test a man can pass.
All I ever wanted was a single thing worth fighting for.
Ladies and gentlemen...
you are not in Kansas any more.
You are on Pandora.
You should see your faces.
We have an indigenous population called the Na'vi.
They are very hard to kill.
This is why we're here.
Because this little grey rock sells for twenty million a kilo.
Their village happens to be resting on the richest deposit,
and they need to relocate.
Those savages are threatening our whole operation.
We're on the brink of war and you're supposed to be finding a diplomatic solution.
The concept is to drive these remotely controlled bodies, called avatars.
They're grown from human DNA... Mixed with DNA of the natives.
A marine, in an avatar body.
That's a potent mix.
You get me what I need, I'll see to it you get your legs back...
Your real legs.
Hell yeah, Sir.
Looks like you.
This is your avatar.
Just relax and let your mind go blank.
That shouldn't be hard for you.
Jake, it's real simple...
I want you to learn from the inside, I want you to gain their trust.
You should not be here.
Go back!
All this is your fault.
I need your help.
Outstanding.
Haven't gotten lost in the woods, have you?
Did you forget what team you're playing for?
The strong prey on the weak...
And nobody does a thing.
You've got one hour.
You knew this would happen?
Everything changed.
Jake, it's crazy here.
Quaritch is rolling and there's no stopping him.
We're going up against gunships with bows and arrows.
Then I guess we'd better stop him.
They've sent us a message...
That they can take whatever they want.
Well we will send them a message...
That this...
This is our land!